Okay I'm Matthew Miller. I work for Red Hat.
我是 Matthew Miller。我在 Red Hat 工作。
And I am the Fedora project leader.
我是 Fedora 项目负责人。
My name is Jonathan Dieter.
我叫 Jonathan Dieter。
I am a system administrator for a school in Beirut, Lebanon.
我是黎巴嫩贝鲁特地区一所学校的系统管理员。
My name is Sumantro
我叫 Sumantro，
I work for Red Hat for Fedora QA team and yeah
我在 Red Hat 的 Fedora QA 部门工作。
我是一名质量工程师。
My name is Mike DePaulo.
我叫 Mike DePaulo。
I contribute to Fedora in my free time.
业余时间我为 Fedora 做一些贡献。
I'm a packager and ambassador.
我是一名打包者，也是一名 （Fedora）大使。
I'm also contributing a little bit to modularity and diversity.
有时我也为模块化和多样性做一点贡献。
so I'm Jona.
我是 Jona。
I'm part of the Albania local community because I come from Albania
我来自阿尔巴尼亚的本地社区。
So my name is Pravin Satpute. I'm from India
我是 Pravin Satpute。我来自印度。
So I'm Mike McGrath.
我是 Mike McGrath。
I work for the platform engineering team as a manager.
我是 (Red Hat) 平台研发团队的一位经理。
I'm Ralph Bean
我是 Ralph Bean，
and I have (been coming to) the flock for five or six years now.
过去五六年我都参加了 Flock。
I used to work on the Fedora engineering team at Red Hat
我曾经在 Red Hat 的 Fedora 工程团队工作，
and so it was my full-time job to work on Fedora and come to flock and work with the community.
所以为 Fedora 工作以及参加 Flock 曾经是我的本职工作的一部分。
So my name is Kanika and I'm from India.
我叫 Kanika，我来自印度。
I've been contributing to fedora for two years now
我已经为 Fedora 做贡献有两年了。
My name is Justin Flory.
我叫 Justin Flory。
I've been a contributor to fedora since November 2015 or so.
2015 年 11 月前后我开始为 Fedora 做贡献。
My name is Ricky Elrod.
我叫 Ricky Elord。
I am on the Fedora engineering team at Red Hat.
目前我在 Red Hat 的 Fedora 研发团队工作。
My name is Brian Exelbierd.
我叫 Brian Exelbierd。
I work for Red Hat as the Fedora Community Action and impact coordinator.
我在 Red Hat 担任 Fedora “社区实践与成效协调人”。
Basically there's a technology side and a people side,
简单来说 (Fedora 社区) 有技术与人员两个方面，
and I think they're both very strong
而且我认为二者都很强。
I think Fedora we do really try and follow the leading edge of open source technology and commitment to the open source part of that.
我认为我们确实努力跟随开源前沿，坚守开源精神。
it not just that it's the bleeding edge
并不只是说最新的代码版本，
but we try to make sure we're following the leading edge of exciting stuff
而是跟随开源技术前沿，
but also getting it to people in a useful way.
并且把它们做得对用户有用。
so I think that's appealing.
所以我认为这个非常有吸引力。
It's a kind of fun stuff to work on at the operating system level
在操作系统层做这些事情挺有趣的。
That's neat.
这样很棒。
but also this is a really amazing group of people
而且 (Fedora 社区) 是一群很给力的人。
and you know we've got thousands of people who contribute every year
我们有数千名贡献者每年都会有所贡献,
two or three thousand people to some level.
大约两三千人。
and a core group of you know maybe four or five hundred people who are working every week on the project
总数约四五百人的一群核心贡献者每周都会为项目付出。
and they're really great generous people who have a real passion for the things we're working on
他们非常慷慨，对他们所做的事情拥有强烈激情，
so I think that's pretty appealing, it's fun
因此我认为这是很动人的，很有意思的。
I happily install most of the any of the nonviolent games in the Fedora repository on our systems
我很高兴地把 Fedora 软件仓库中的大多数非暴力游戏安装在系统中。
And I'm like how that is.
我就是如此。
The major part of Fedora where is what I love about is it's a bleeding edge
最让我喜欢 Fedora 的地方是它的前卫，
so I get the latest and the greatest of whatever that I want.
因此我可以获取我想用的软件的最新最好版本。
Be it building bleeding edge stuff on IOT or build big data
无论是构建物联网还是大数据领域前沿的东西，
I have whatever tools that I require in that to make sure my project is up and running.
我能获取任何我需要的工具从而使我的项目启动运行。
one of the things that I think is critical about Fedora that we are doing a better and better job messaging on this.
我认为 Fedora 很关键的一点是我们传播了正确的信息。
the Fedora community is way more than the production of the operating system
Fedora 社区远远不止发布一个操作系统。
there's a lot of things to do and you can get involved in them
有很多可以做的事情，
you know there isn't like territorialism like you can contribute to this component only we contribute this components.
这儿没有例如你只能为某个模块做贡献而只有我能为这个模块做贡献这样的属地主义，
I think Fedora values the contributors.
我认为 Fedora 重视贡献者。
The thing that I think is really important about Fedora
我觉得 Fedora 很重要的一部分是
is we provide a facility for people to do what they want to do
Fedora 提供了一些设施从而使得人们可以做他们想做的事情，
and they can get a lot of support from their fellow community members
并且可以从社区成员中获得很多帮助，
because we bring the right kinds of people together.
因为我们把对的人聚集在一起了。
and I think the the amazing thing for me is not just how many old faces I still that are there
我觉得最令人振奋的的不是我仍然能见到多少熟悉的面孔
but how many new faces I see
而是我能见到多少新面孔。
And how important it is to the community to get people involved in and get out of their way.
以及吸引新人加入并且不去干涉是多么的重要。
and I think there's not just the common sense of shared purpose towards building Fedora the operating system and the distribution
我认为共同理念不只是打造 Fedora 操作系统发行版，
and making sure that our users are happy
并且让用户满意。
but there is a shared understanding that we're all people
还包括我们都是活生生的人
we're all flawed
人无完人，
we all have something to bring to the table and so
三人行必有我师，
with let's come and talk and and figure out you know what needs to happen what we can do
集思广益，搞明白需要做什么我们能做什么。
and you know everybody sees everybody else has important I think
并且每个人都觉得其他人是重要的，
it's a very unique a very unique experience everybody's kind of at the same level here. It's great.
这里大家比较平等，这是一种非常独特的体验。这样很棒。
the community by far I mean people are the people I work with are some of the smartest people I know.
我是说与我共识的社区成员是我认识的最聪明的人，
they're very resourceful
他们知识渊博，
they are nice
他们为人友善，
I mean I just I can't say enough about it
我完全无法用语言形容。
I just I love the community
总之我非常热爱这个社区。
it's like a family.
它像一个大家庭。
Fedora, I will say like anyone who is coming to the fedora
就像其他人所说那样，
so he will not feel that there is not for him anything
任何加入社区的人都会感受到归属感。
so there is for everyone there is something in Fedora.
每个人都能从 Fedora 中找到适合自己的事情。
it's a it's it's passionate but very friendly
社区非常有激情并且很友善。
and you see that especially in Flock
并且在 Flock 这里非常明显。
I mean it's a really a really technical group of people
我是说，Flock 是一群技术很强的人
that like working together and love working on what they are working on
喜爱他们所做的事情并且聚集到一起来工作，
and it's a fun place to be
Flock 是个非常有趣的地方。
I could easily see how passionate people were not just about the work that they were doing but
我可以很容易得看到人们不仅对他们所做的事情有激情，
also about supporting each other
并且他们也会相互支持，
As they can empowering an inclusive community to build better software together.
这使得一个包罗万象的社区共同制作更好的软件成为可能。
let's say the community it's one of the main reasons why I'm still part of it
或许可以说社区是我仍然参与 Fedora 的重要原因之一。
because they are really friendly there.
因为成员们都特别友好，
they are really friendly to the newcomers especially
他们对新人尤其友好，
so you feel really welcomed at the community
因此你在社区中会觉得受到欢迎。
because, you know, when you go to a community to a new community and you want to be part of it,
要知道，想参与到社区并且成为社区一员，
first of all you are afraid that someone might
首先你会担心的就是有人说：
say "okay but you don't know this question?" but not at all.
“哦？你连这个问题都不知道！”，但这不会发生。
they will be really friendly with you they they will support you for everything that you might need
社区成员会尽最大努力帮助你。
and they will show you even the right direction where to go and
他们会为你指引正确的方向，
which teams you can be inside.
以及哪些团队你可以参与其中。
large community of people who kind of use open source as an excuse to change the world
社区成员利用开源作为改变社会的理由，
which that's an easy thing to say.
说起来容易，
but we do it a lot through non-code contributions.
但是我们也从非技术角度做出贡献。
we have a huge outreach program
我们有一个很大的社区推广项目，
program we have huge marketing opportunities
我们有很多市场方面的机遇、
writing opportunities
写作方面的机遇。
there's ways for people to become involved in the ideals of open source
开源社区中总有适合人们的贡献机会。
even if they choose not to actually commit a line of what we as engineers would call source
甚至即使他们不打算贡献任何一行工程师们称之为代码的东西都可以
中文字幕： Fedora 中文用户组